http://www.nttinc.com/privacy-policy/

Electrical Safety Training Programs
2021 Arc Flash Electrical Safety [Based on NFPA 70E®]
Electrical Safety: NFPA 70E Overview
- NEW!
Electrical Safety Awareness
- NEW!
Electrical Safety Practical Skills for Switchgear
Electrical Safety: Power Generation, Transmission & Distribution [based on OSHA 1910.269]
Upcoming Training Programs
01/11
-
01/12
:
Seattle
, WA
2021 Arc Flash Electrical Safety [Based on NFPA 70E®]
01/25
-
01/26
:
Sacramento
, CA
2021 Arc Flash Electrical Safety [Based on NFPA 70E®]
01/25
-
01/26
:
Centennial
, CO
2021 Arc Flash Electrical Safety [Based on NFPA 70E®]
02/01
-
02/02
:
Live Online Training
, CO
2021 Arc Flash Electrical Safety [Based on NFPA 70E®]
02/05
-
02/05
:
Live Online Training
, CO
Electrical Safety: NFPA 70E Overview
- NEW!
View All
Electrical Safety Training Programs
Top
Electrical Electrical Compliance Training Programs
2017 NFPA 70® – National Electrical Code® [NEC]
2020 NFPA 70® – National Electrical Code® [NEC]
Electrical Systems: SOARS Grounding & Bonding
Electrical Systems: Hazardous Locations
NEC® – Analysis of Changes 2020 with Practical Exercises
NFPA 110® – Emergency & Standby Power Systems
NFPA 70B® – Recommended Practice for Electrical Equipment Maintenance®
NFPA 72: National Fire Alarm & Signaling Code®
2018 NFPA 79® – Electrical Standard For Industrial Machinery®
NICET I & II
National Electrical Safety Code® [NESC]
01/15
:
Seattle
, WA
2020 NFPA 70® - National Electrical Code® [NEC]
01/27
-
01/29
:
Sacramento
, CA
2020 NFPA 70® - National Electrical Code® [NEC]
01/27
-
01/29
:
Centennial
, CO
2020 NFPA 70® - National Electrical Code® [NEC]
02/03
-
02/05
:
Live Online Training
, CO
2020 NFPA 70® - National Electrical Code® [NEC]
02/10
-
02/12
:
Riverside
, CA
2020 NFPA 70® - National Electrical Code® [NEC]
PLCs [Programmable Logic Controllers]: Automation Systems
PLCs [Programmable Logic Controllers]: ControlLogix & RSLogix 5000
PLCs [Programmable Logic Controllers]: Fundamentals
PLCs [Programmable Logic Controllers]: Siemens Simatic S7
Tuning DDC/Process Control Loops
Variable Frequency Drives [VFD]
Upcoming Training Programs
01/26
-
01/28
:
02/25
:
03/03
:
03/05
:
03/11
:
01/14
:
01/28
:
02/11
:
02/10
:
02/11
:
Boilers: An Operational Workshop
HVAC: Brazing [Advanced]
01/12
:
02/09
:
02/11
:
03/10
:
03/09
:
OSHA 30 Hour Safety
HAZWOPER: Refresher [8 hr]
HAZWOPER: Technician & Specialist [24 hr]
Upcoming Seminars
Call 1.800.922.2820 for more info
on schedule and pricing.
03/04
:
03/12
:
03/26
:
04/16
:
05/07
:
03/18
:
05/06
:
06/09
:
06/11
:
08/26
:
All Mechanical Maintenance Training Programs
Select the following link if you would like to recover a report that has been previously deleted.
Search site for...
Privacy Policy
NTT, Inc. collects information from visitors who access our web site to register for courses or request information. Information we collect is used for securing order information and to provide a customized experience for you. Your information will generally not be shared with third parties. We may only disclose personal information that you have provided if we have received your permission beforehand, for special partner promotions or when disclosure is required by law. We also utilize your information to send you communications about NTT programs and you may opt out of these communications at any time.
Data Security Commitment
NTT is committed to protecting the security of your personal information. Our website has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. We use a variety of security technologies and procedures to help protect your personal information from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. For example, we store the personal information you provide in computer servers with limited access that are located in controlled facilities. When we transmit sensitive information (such as a credit card number) over the internet, we protect it through the use of encryption, such as the Secure Socket Layer (SSL) protocol. While we make every effort to ensure the integrity and security of our network and systems, we cannot guarantee that our security measures will prevent third-party “hackers” from illegally obtaining this information. Remember that any information you may disclose in any public areas of our web site or on the Internet becomes public information. Exercise caution when you decide to disclose personal information in public areas.
Third party vendor’s collection of information. NTT Training uses third party advertising platforms and vendors that may use cookies to serve ads on other sites, based on your visit to NTT Training.
Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.
User options regarding collection of information. With regard to automatically collected information, it is standard practice for many Web sites to collect non-personally identifiable information about your Web browser, operating system, IP address and browsing history (i.e. what pages on our Web site you viewed). Any other non-personal information collected through the use of cookies, may be opted out of by disabling or rejecting cookies. (Cookies are short pieces of information used by Web browsers to remember information provided by the user.) With regard to personal information collected through our Web site, you may opt out of NTT Training marketing solicitations at any time by completing a contact form at www.nttinc.com/contact.
Online Course Registration Privacy
When you register for courses online, you will be asked to provide personal information including name, address, telephone number, billing information (such as a credit card number), and the type of personal computer being used to access our web site. If you are registering on behalf of someone else (such as registering one or more employees) you will be asked to provide information about each participant including the participants’ names, addresses, and phone numbers. The information collected during the registration process is used to manage each registrant’s personal account (such as for billing purposes). This information is not shared with third parties, unless specifically stated. Exceptions occur where NTT, Inc. and a partner jointly promote our programs. NTT, Inc. may provide the partner certain personal information, such as the name, address, and user name of persons who registered for a course as a result of the joint promotion for the sole purpose of allowing us and the partner to assess the results of the promotion. In this instance, personal information may not be used by the partner for any other purpose. NTT, Inc. may also generate non-identifying and aggregate profiles from personal information that visitors provide during registration (such as the total number, but not the names, of visitors). We may use this aggregated and non-identifying information to improve course offerings and develop product communications based on customer needs.
Online Promotional Communications
On our web site, you can submit personal information in order to receive materials such as our Course Catalog or registration packet. We share aggregated and non-identifying information about our visitors collected from these requests, as well as through online surveys and promotions. We may use this aggregated and non-identifying information to deliver promotional communications via mail or email. For instance, if we want to contact electrical workers based upon the aggregated and non-identifying information we have collected, we may send an email, mail piece or other communication about our products to this audience. NTT, Inc. does not share personal information about its visitors with third parties except in the case of joint partner promotions (detailed above).
Responses to Email Inquiries
When visitors send email inquiries to NTT, Inc., the return email address is used to answer the email inquiry we receive. NTT, Inc. may use the return email address for sending visitors information by email, and does occasionally share the return email address with a third party.
Special Cases
It is NOT our policy to use or share personal information about visitors in ways unrelated to the ones described above without also providing you an opportunity to opt out or otherwise prohibit such unrelated uses. We may disclose personal information about visitors or information regarding your use of NTT, Inc. web site, for any reason if, in our sole discretion, it is required to satisfy laws, such as the Electronic Communications Privacy Act, regulations, or governmental or legal requests for such information; to disclose information that is necessary to identify, contact, or bring legal action against someone who may be violating the law, or to protect NTT, Inc. and our visitors.
Questions or to Change Your Profile Information
You may modify or delete the personal information we have collected from you. To change your information, or if you have any questions about this Privacy Policy or the practices described herein, contact our Customer Service Department at 800-922-2820.
Revisions to This Policy
NTT, Inc. reserves the right to revise, amend, or modify this policy, and our other policies and agreements at any time and in any manner. Notice of any revision, amendment, or modification will be posted.
Copyright Infringement Policy for NTT Training Content
What is copyright infringement?
Copyright protection applies to original works of authorship fixed in a tangible form of expression including, but not limited to, written materials such as textbooks and manuals, web content such as multimedia presentations, videos and audio files, as well as other forms of print and digital information. The owner of copyright has exclusive rights to reproduce, display and/or prepare derivative works of the copyrighted work, and to distribute copies of the copyrighted work to the public by sale or other transfer or ownership, or by rental, lease or lending. Copyright infringement is the violation of any of a copyright owner’s exclusive rights. It is the act of exercising, without permission or legal authority, one or more of the exclusive rights granted to the copyright owner under section 106 of the Copyright Act (Title 17 of the United States Code). Reproducing or distributing a copyrighted work (in the file-sharing context, this means downloading or uploading substantial parts of a copyrighted work without authority) constitutes an act of copyright infringement.
Examples of copyright infringement of NTT Training Content
These examples constitute illegal copyright infringement and are subject to criminal and civil penalties.
Unauthorized duplication, distribution or use of NTT classroom training materials such as textbooks, PowerPoint presentations and any other learning materials provided.
Unauthorized duplication, distribution or use of NTT online training content, including computer software, online courses, skills assessments, sound or video recordings, training data and reports.
Unauthorized duplication, distribution or use of NTT web site content, including NTT-authored articles and case histories, sound or video recordings, photos and graphics, etc.
NTT Response to Unauthorized Distribution of Copyrighted Material
NTT responds to legitimate notices or letters of illegal copyright infringement based on the requirements of the Digital Millennium Copyright Act and directs institution administrative management to investigate and respond. NTT will cooperate fully with any investigation by public authorities related to illegally copied or downloaded copyrighted information. Anyone found guilty will be subject to the full extent of fines and penalties imposed.
Copyright Infringement Penalties
Penalties for copyright infringement include civil and criminal penalties. In general, anyone found liable for civil copyright infringement may be ordered to pay either actual damages or “statutory” damages affixed at not less than $750 and not more than $30,000 per work infringed. For “willful” infringement, a court may award up to $150,000 per work infringed. A court can, in its discretion, also assess costs and attorney fees. For details, see Title 17, United States Code, Sections 504, 505. Willful copyright infringement can also result in criminal penalties, including imprisonment of up to five years and fines of up to $250,000 per offense.
Who should you contact to report a claim of copyright infringement?
Contact NTT at 1-800-922-2820 and ask to speak to a manager.
Attendance Monitoring Policy and Procedure
Policy Purpose
The purpose of this policy is to monitor student attendance to ensure compliance with the requirements and policies re the issuance of Certificates of Completion. The intent is to provide all students with the best opportunity to achieve the learning outcomes of their chosen class.
Policy Scope
This policy applies to all classes whether they are considered “mobile” or “onsite”.
Policy Content
Instructors will closely monitor the sign-in sheet each day in order to ensure that students attending class are properly identified and that those who sign in remain in the class throughout the day. The monitoring process is repeated for each day of that class. Attendance will be taken twice each class day and recorded on the sign-in sheet, once at the beginning of the day and again after lunch.
Attendance monitoring is the only means to ensure that students meet the requirements stipulated to receive a Certificate of Completion. 80% attendance is required as a minimum.
This policy is made available to instructors and students through the Institute’s website.
Recordkeeping and Confidentiality
Records of all attendance handled under this policy and their outcomes will be maintained for a period of at least five years in SLX for auditing purposes by senior management or ACCET. The general policy of NTT is not to provide access to customer-student information to third parties, absent the written consent of the customer-student. You can unsubscribe from NTT emails, or all NTT materials, by clicking Unsubscribe or contacting 1-800-922-2820.
Publication
These procedures are to be published for students, instructors and staff on the Institute’s website to ensure that current and prospective students and staff have up to date and accurate information available to them.
NTT Complaint Procedure
Students or clients who feel that they did not receive the value they expected from any NTT training program will have their enrollment fee returned, no strings attached.
If this unconditional money-back guarantee does not satisfy the concerns of the student or client, they can submit a written complaint to the attention of NTT Management, who will address the issue. A written response will be made within ten business days from the receipt of the complaint. The staff and instructors of NTT are committed to assist clients and students as much as possible to resolve any issues that affect successful training.
Notice to Students: ACCET Complaint Procedure
This institution is recognized by the Accrediting Council for Continuing Education & Training (ACCET) as meeting and maintaining certain standards of quality. It is the mutual goal of ACCET and the institution to ensure that educational training programs of quality are provided. When problems arise, students should make every attempt to find a fair and reasonable solution through the institution’s internal complaint procedure, which is required of ACCET accredited institutions. NTT’s written complaint procedure is published on the institution’s website or otherwise available from the institution, upon request. Note that ACCET will process complaints which involve ACCET standards and policies and, therefore, are within the scope of the accrediting agency.
In the event that a student has exercised the institution’s formal student complaint procedure, and the problem(s) have not been resolved, the student has the right and is encouraged to take the following steps:
1. Complaints should be submitted in writing and mailed, or emailed to the ACCET office. Complaints received by phone will be documented, but the complainant will be requested to submit the complaint in writing.
The letter of complaint must contain the following:
Name and location of the ACCET institution;
A detailed description of the alleged problem(s);
The approximate date(s) that the problem(s) occurred;
The names and titles/positions of all individual(s) involved in the problem(s), including faculty, staff, and/or other students;
What was previously done to resolve the complaint, along with evidence demonstrating that the institution’s complaint procedure was followed prior to contacting ACCET;
The name, email address, telephone number, and mailing address of the complainant. If the complainant specifically requests that anonymity be maintained, ACCET will not reveal his or her name to the institution involved; and
The status of the complainant with the institution (e.g. current student, former student, etc.).
In addition to the letter of complaint, copies of any relevant supporting documentation should be forwarded to ACCET (e.g. student’s enrollment agreement, syllabus or course outline, correspondence between the student and the institution).
SEND TO: ACCET
CHAIR, COMPLAINT REVIEW COMMITTEE
1722 N Street, NW
Washington, DC 20036
Telephone: (202) 955-1113
Fax: (202) 955-1118 or (202) 955-5306
Email: complaints@accet.org
Website: www.accet.org
Note: Complainants will receive an acknowledgment of receipt within 15 days.
SKILLED WORKERS. STRONGER COMPANIES
NTT Training
CAREERS AT NTT
Training Schedule
On-Site Training
Self Paced Online Training
Live Online Training
Blog
About NTT
Resources
NTT in the News
Contact
Sitemap
Call now855.712.7353
Our Mission:"Deliver solutions to our clients (and their global workforce) designed for safety, productivity and profitability.”NTT Training Inc. has been accredited by the
Accrediting Council for Continuing Education & Training (ACCET).
ACCET accreditation serves the interests of companies, agencies, and the public through the establishment of standards, policies, and procedures in conjunction with an objective third-party professional evaluation designed to identify and inspire sound education and training practices.
Better Business Bureau
A Training Division of ECPI University
© 2020-2021 NTT Inc. All Rights Reserved
Policies
Terms and Conditions
Chat
Now
